so let's look at our tomasulo's
algorithm quiz solution does it issue
instructions in program order yes it
does instructions come from the
instruction buffer in program order and
that's the order in which we're going to
issue them you cannot issue instructions
out of order so this is true we don't
select it because the question is which
is not true it dispatches instructions
in program order no it doesn't
instructions can they be dispatched
outside of program order that's why this
is an out of order processor so this is
definitely not true and then it writes
results in program order
not necessarily again results can be
written in the order in which they are
produced and it works for that so this
is not true so basically the only one
that is true is one the other two are
not true so we selected the two and
three as not true